Finding Aid for Extension Service (University of Michigan) publications, 1911-1996
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Extension Service (University of Michigan) publications 1911-1996
University of Michigan. Extension Service.
1 oversize volumes
17 linear feet
03111 Bimu 2
Publications produced by the Extension Service and its subunits including bulletins and course listings, reports, newsletters and manuals.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The publications record group (donor no. 1660 ) came to the library in a number of accessions beginning in the 1950s.
No further additions to the records expected.
The collection is open without restriction.
See the history in finding aid for Extension Service (University of Michigan) records.
The Extension Service publications consist of publications produced by the Extension Service and its subunits and include bulletins and course listings, reports, newsletters and manuals and other printed items. The material is divided into three series: Unit Publications, Sub-unit Publications and Topical Publications.
Unit Publications include bulletins concerning credit and non-credit courses, reports and a run of the newsletter Extension Service News, whose title later became U-M Extension. Sub-unit Publications consist of material produced by units under the control of the Extension Service. These include the Audio-Visual Education Center and the Michigan High School Forensic Association. Records of the Broadcasting Service will be found in the WUOM record group. Topical Publications contain pamphlets and brochures pertaining to conferences and institutes and various other programs sponsored or produced by the Extension Service. Printed material will also be found scattered throughout the record group.
Subjects:
Adult education--Michigan.; Education--Michigan.; Fire prevention--Study and teaching.; University extension--Michigan.; University of Michigan. Extension Service.; Civil defense--Michigan.; Aging--Study and teaching.; Geriatrics--Michigan--Study and teaching.; World War, 1939-1945--Education and the war.; Upper Peninsula (Mich.); Civilian Conservation Corps (U.S.)--Michigan.
Genre Terms:
Bulletins.; Manuals.; Reports.; Brochures.; Newsletters.; Study guides.
- Unit Publications
  - Annual Reports
    - Report of the University Extension Service, 1938-1942, 1943/1944 (Box 1)
    - Report to the President, 1944/1945-1978/1979, 4 folders (Box 1)
  - Brochures
    - General Information and Course Regulations, 1953-1995 (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 1)
  - Bulletins
    - 1911-1946, 18 folders; 4 volumes (Box 1)
    - 1946-1956, 9 folders; 7 volumes (Box 2)
    - 1956-1962, 6 folders; 6 volumes (Box 3)
    - 1962-1968, 2 folders; 6 volumes (Box 4)
    - 1968/1985-1994, 18 folders; 3 volumes (Box 5)
    - Courses for Adults
      - 1962-1972, 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Field Biology for Science Teachers, 1976-1977 (Box 5)
    - Graduate Courses in Occupational Education, 1977-1981
      - Graduate Professional Programs in Engineering, 1963-1980 (Box 5)
    - Landscape Design Study Course, 1960-1968 (Box 5)
    - Library Science 1971-1977 (Box 5)
    - Spring/Summer Session Catalogue 1996 (Box 5)
    - Teaching Technical and Professional Writing, 1975-1978 (Box 5)
  - Histories
    - History of the Saginaw Area Center of the University of Michigan, 1945-1955 (Box 6)
  - Manuals
    - The Fireman and Electrical Equipment, 1952 (Box 6)
    - Help Yourself to Efficient Reading, 1953 (Box 6)
    - Organizing a Community Council, 1953 (Box 6)
  - Newsletters
    - Extension Service News (continues as The Extension Service News)
      - Volume 1 1941-1942 also in a bound volume. (Box 6)
    - The Extension Service News (continues as Extension Service News)
      - Volumes 2-30 1942-1971, 29 folders (Box 6)
      - Volumes 2-10 (Volume 1)
    - Extension Service News (continues as U-M Extension)
      - Volumes 31-36 1971-1977, 6 folders (Box 6)
    - U-M Extension
      - Volumes 37-40 1977-1981, 4 folders (Box 6)
    - The Upper Peninsula Concert Series Newsletter, 1957-1958 (Box 6)
  - Pamphlets
    - Cooperative Plan for Community Center Service in Michigan, 1925-1928 (Box 6)
    - Life in the Family, [1952] (Box 6)
    - Parent's Exchange, [1953-1954] (Box 6)
    - A Program in Parental Education, [1930/1931]-1933/1934 (Box 6)
  - Reports
    - Adult Education in the Modern University, 1949 (Box 6)
    - Education in Citizenship: The Organization of a Citizenship Program for Young Voters, 1940 (Box 6)
    - The Extension Service Self-Study, 1963 (Box 6)
    - It's Happening Here, 1939 (Box 6)
    - A Philosophy of Extension for the University of Michigan, 1963 (Box 6)
    - A Study of the Supervised College Correspondence Study Department, 1938 (Box 6)
    - The University Extension Service, 1961 (Box 6)
  - Summer Symposia 1951 (Box 6)
  - Syllabus
    - Telecourse Syllabus
      - Man in His World: Human Biology, 1950-1951 (Box 6)
- Sub-Unit Publications
  - Adult Education Program
    - Directories
      - Community Directory 1944-1945 (Box 7)
    - Manuals
      - Invigorating Community Meetings 1943 (Box 7)
    - Newsletters
      - Community Action
        - 1943-1945 (Box 7)
      - Michigan Community News
        - Volumes 1-4 1939-1942, 4 folders (Box 7)
    - Reports
      - What Some Communities Have Done for Themselves: A List of Activities of Community-Wide Benefit, 1941 (Box 7)
      - Youth Center Evaluation, 1946 (Box 7)
  - Audio-Visual Education Center
    - Calendars
      - Educational Film Showings, 1949-1951 (Box 7)
    - Catalogs
      - Audio Tape Recordings, 1971 (Box 7)
      - Catalog of Educational Motion Pictures, 1963 (Box 7)
      - Educational Film Catalog, 1976 (Box 7)
      - Educational Films, 1973 (Box 7)
      - Educational Motion Pictures, Filmstrips, Lantern Slides, Recordings, 1947 (Box 7)
      - Film Directory, 1955 (Box 7)
      - Film Supplement, 1953-1954 (Box 7)
      - Films for the Campus, 1947 (Box 7)
      - Motion Pictures, 1952 (Box 7)
      - Motion Pictures, Filmstrips, Slides, Recordings, Exhibits, 1949-1950 (Box 7)
    - Programs
      - The American Negro, Undated (Box 7)
  - Bureau of School Services
    - Michigan School Testing Service
      - Reports
        - Personalizing Test Use: A Counselor's Casebook, 1965 (Box 7)
        - Testing Programs in Michigan Schools, 1963 (Box 7)
  - Bureau of Visual Education
    - Catalogs
      - Instructional Motion Pictures, 1940/1941-1944 (Box 7)
    - Manuals
      - Film Utilization Guide, 1942 (Box 7)
  - Community Adult Education
    - Bibliographies
      - Selected References on Community Councils 1948 (Box 8)
    - Brochures (Box 8)
    - Catalogs
      - What Some Communities Have Done for Themselves: A Catalog of Community Activities, 1951 (Box 8)
    - Directories
      - Directory of Community Councils in Michigan, 1949-1950 (Box 8)
      - Michigan Community Council Community Directory, 1946 (Box 8)
    - Manuals
      - The Community Calendar, 1953 (Box 8)
      - Invigorating Community Meetings, 1946 (Box 8)
    - Newsletters
      - Community Action, 1946 (Box 8)
      - The Michigan Community News Letter
        - Volumes 5-14 1947-1958, 10 folders (Box 8)
  - Community and Adult Education Department
    - Brochures Undated (Box 8)
    - Directories
      - Community Councils in Detroit, 1965 (Box 8)
      - Directory of Community Councils in Michigan, 1965-1967 (Box 8)
    - Newsletters
      - The Michigan Newsletter on Community Development and Education
        - Volumes 15-16 1960-1961, 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Continuing Education Unit
    - Brochures Undated (Box 8)
    - Manuals
      - Criteria and Procedures to be Used for the Continuing Education Unit at the University of Michigan, 1975 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence Study Department
    - Bulletins 1932-1965, 1 folders; 1 volumes (Box 8)
    - Syllabus
      - Independent Study Through Correspondence: English Composition, 1966 (Box 8)
  - Department of Conferences and Institutes
    - Calendars 1973-1979 (Box 8)
  - Department of Independent Study
    - Brochures
      - Course Listings (Box 8)
      - General (Box 8)
    - Bulletins
      - Learning Through Independent Study (Box 8)
  - Department of Lectures and Program Planning
    - Brochures Undated (Box 8)
  - Detroit Center
    - Bulletins 1950-1965 (Box 8)
  - The Detroit Program
    - Bulletins 1943-1945 (Box 8)
  - Division of Adult Education
    - Brochures
      - Programs of Insurance Study, 1958-1959 (Box 8)
    - Bulletins 1958-1960 (Box 8)
  - Extension Gaming Service
    - Brochures 1973-1977 (Box 8)
  - Firemanship Training Program
    - Brochures
      - General 1961-1981, 3 folders (Box 8)
      - Instructor's Conference, 1959-1981 (Box 8)
      - Miscellaneous Undated (Box 8)
    - Brochures (cont.)
      - Newsletters
        - Michigan Fire Service Bulletin
          - Volume 1 1957 (Box 8)
          - Volume 3 1959 (Box 8)
  - Flint Center
    - Bulletins 1950-1966 (Box 8)
  - Graduate Study Center at Dearborn (Box 8)
  - Lecture Bureau
    - Brochures Undated (Box 8)
  - Library Extension Service
    - Bulletins 1942-1952 (Box 8)
    - Pamphlets
      - A Suggested Bookshelf for Parent Education, [1945] (Box 8)
      - Suggested Readings from the Adult Education Institute 1933-1937 (Box 8)
  - Metropolitan Detroit Center
    - Newsletters
      - UMEX Newscoop
        - Volumes 1-11 1950-1958, 2 folders (Box 8)
        - 1960-1963 (Box 8)
  - Michigan High School Debating League
    - Brochures 1929-1930 (Box 8)
    - Constitution 1918 (Box 8)
    - Programs
      - State Championship Debate, 1927-1933 (Box 8)
    - Schedules
      - Schedule of Debates, 1920-1921 (Box 8)
  - Michigan High School Forensic Association
    - Brochures
      - Awards and Scholarships, 1962-1963 (Box 8)
    - Bulletins
      - 1933/1934-1950/1951, 3 folders (Box 8)
  - Michigan High School Forensic Association (cont.)
    - Manuals
      - Speech Activities, 1960-1967, 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Newsletters
      - Forensic News
        - 1960/1961-1963/1964, 4 folders (Box 8)
        - 1964/1965-1966/1967, 3 folders (Box 9)
    - Programs
      - The Detroit Free Press $2,800 Debate Scholarship Contest, 1955-1961 (Box 9)
      - State Championship Debate, 1934-1968, 3 folders (Box 9)
  - Office of Community College Services
    - Brochures
      - Undated 1975-1977 (Box 9)
  - Office of Community College Services (cont.)
    - Newsletters
      - Community College Newsletter
        - Volume 4 1976-1977 (Box 9)
        - Volume 9 1982-1983 (Box 9)
  - Real Estate Program
    - Bulletins
      - Courses 1972-1976 (Box 9)
      - Courses and Institutes 1976-1980 (Box 9)
      - General 1981-1982 (Box 9)
      - Institutes 1968-1980 (Box 9)
    - Directories
      - Real Estate Alumni of Michigan, 1958-1965 (Box 9)
    - Proceedings
      - Michigan Real Estate Clinic, 1954-1960, 3 folders (Box 9)
    - Programs
      - Real Estate Clinic, 1949-1978, 2 folders (Box 9)
      - Recognition Exercises, 1962-1980 (Box 9)
  - University Center
    - Bulletins 1969-1972 (Box 9)
  - University Center for Adult Education
    - Bulletins 1966-1974, 8 folders (Box 9)
    - Programs
      - Detroit Adventure, 1960-1967 (Box 9)
  - University Consortium Center
    - Brochures
      - General 1975 (Box 9)
    - Bulletins 1974-1979, 3 folders (Box 9)
    - Miscellaneous 1979-1980 (Box 9)
  - University Courses in Adult Education
    - Bulletins 1975-1980, 6 folders (Box 9)
  - Upper Peninsula Office
    - Brochures 1957 (Box 9)
- Topical Publications
  - Administration of National Parks and Equivalent Reserves 1965-1981, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Adult Education Institute
    - Announcements 1935-1950 (Box 10)
    - Pamphlets
      - Study Outline by the Library Extension Service 1939-1944 (Box 10)
    - Proceedings
      - Proceedings of the Fifth Annual Adult Education Institute, 1937 (Box 10)
    - Programs 1932-1962 (Box 10)
  - Age of Opportunity, 1956-1963 (Box 10)
  - Alumni University, 1933-1969, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Annual Student Librarian Assistants Association of Michigan, 1959-1970 (Box 10)
  - Annual Pharmacy Lectures, 1953-1967 (Box 10)
  - Assertiveness Training, 1977 (Box 10)
  - Backgrounds and Horizons Program, 1935-1937 (Box 10)
  - Basic Income Tax Institutes, 1976-1978 (Box 10)
  - Center for the Continuing Education of Women 1965-1970 (Box 10)
  - Center for the Study of Higher Education 1975-1978 (Box 10)
  - Coal Utilization Institute, 1937-1948 (Box 10)
  - Cognitive Science Society, 1982-1989 (Box 10)
  - Concrete Conference, 1950-1953 (Box 10)
  - Conference for School Board Members, 1948-1973 (Box 10)
  - Conference for Teachers in Driver Education, 1953-1968 (Box 10)
  - Conference for Top Management Automobile Transporters, 1950-1952 (Box 10)
  - Conference on Applied Linguistics, 1969-1981 (Box 10)
  - Conference on Great Lakes Research, 1959-1977 (Box 10)
  - Conference on Human Relations, 1957-1960 (Box 10)
  - Conference on Individual Onsite Wastewater Systems, 1979-1980 (Box 10)
  - Conference on Industrial Relations, 1949-1950 (Box 10)
  - Conference on Organ Music, 1962-1980 (Box 10)
  - Conference on Personnel Management, 1953-1960 (Box 10)
  - Conferences and Courses
    - Miscellaneous
      - 1933-1955, 20 folders (Box 10)
      - 1956-1969, 14 folders (Box 11)
      - 1970-1994, 22 folders (Box 12)
  - Congress of the Guild of Carillonneurs in North America, 1948-1978 (Box 13)
  - Conservation Conference, 1952-1954 (Box 13)
  - Community College Trustee-President's Conference, 1965-1966 (Box 13)
  - CREE: Combined Resources for Educative Electronics, 1972-1973 (Box 13)
  - Department of Speech
    - Manuals
      - Speech Communication in Business and Industry, 1953 (Box 13)
    - Proceedings
      - Speech Communication in Business and Industry, 1959 (Box 13)
    - Programs
      - Speech Communication in Business and Industry, 1953-1961 (Box 13)
      - Summer Speech Conference, 1962-1969 (Box 13)
  - Department of Vocational Education and Practical Arts
    - Miscellaneous (Box 13)
    - Programs
      - Institute for General Shop Teachers, 1954-1963 (Box 13)
      - Institute for Teachers of Auto Mechanics, 1954-1963 (Box 13)
      - Institute for Teachers of Machine Shop and Teachers of Drafting, 1954-1963 (Box 13)
      - Institute for Teachers of Woodworking, 1953-1962 (Box 13)
  - Design and Evaluation of Protection Against Radioactive Fallout, 1961-1962 (Box 13)
  - Economic Outlook, 1958-1984 (Box 13)
  - Education Conferences, 1957-1958 (Box 13)
  - Elements of Civil Defense and Defense Mobilization, 1959-1960 (Box 13)
  - Emergency Medical Service in the Fire Service, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
  - Engineering Science and Management Defense Training, 1941-1942 (Box 13)
  - Esalen Conferences 1975-1977 (Box 13)
  - Estate Tax Seminars, 1976-1978 (Box 13)
  - Federated Garden Clubs of Michigan 1948-1965 (Box 13)
  - Fire Control Seminar, 1957-1987 (Box 13)
  - Foremen's Conference, 1939-1955 (Box 13)
  - The Freshman Year in Science and Engineering, 1990 (Box 13)
  - Health Education Program 1928-1930 (Box 13)
  - Health Occupations Educators Workshop, 1975-1977 (Box 13)
  - High School French Horn Workshop Ensemble, 1962-1980 (Box 13)
  - The Initial Management of the Acutely Ill or Injured Patient, 1966-1972 (Box 13)
  - Institute for Building Officials, 1955-1959 (Box 13)
  - Institute for Community College Board Members and Presidents, 1971-1973 (Box 13)
  - Institute for Instruction and Training in Driver Education, 1948-1949 (Box 13)
  - Institute for Law-Enforcement Officers, 1934-1936 (Box 13)
  - Institute for Mayors and Councilmen
    - Notebook 1962 (Box 13)
    - Programs 1957-1962 (Box 13)
  - Institute for Public Library Trustees, 1947-1948 (Box 13)
  - Institute for the Study of Mental Retardation 1970-1972 (Box 13)
  - Institute in Human Relations, 1956-1960 (Box 13)
  - Institute of Adult Education, 1932-1938 (Box 13)
  - Institute of Gerontology
    - Conference on Aging
      - Brochures 1951-1973 (Box 13)
      - Programs 1951-1970 (Box 13)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 13)
  - Institute of Labor, 1933 (Box 14)
  - Institute of Science and Technology
    - Housing Conferences 1971-1973 (Box 14)
    - Workshops 1964-1969 (Box 14)
  - Institute of Teacher Preparation for Driver Education, 1950-1963 (Box 14)
  - Institute on College and University Administration
    - Brochures 1963-1969 (Box 14)
    - Programs 1960-1969 (Box 14)
  - International Conference on Structural Design of Asphalt Pavement, 1962-1977 (Box 14)
  - Jazz Revisited Colloquium, 1971-1980 (Box 14)
  - Juvenile Court Seminar, 1970 (Box 14)
  - Labor Relations Workshop for Municipal Officials, 1968-1972 (Box 14)
  - Leadership Training Conference, 1967-1968 (Box 14)
  - Leadership Training Workshop, 1962-1964 (Box 14)
  - Linguistic Society of America 1965-1967 (Box 14)
  - Living in the Later Years, 1949-1952 (Box 14)
  - Management Briefing Seminars, 1970-1989 (Box 14)
  - Managing a Small Business, 1979-1980 (Box 14)
  - Mathematics Education Conference, 1952-1975 (Box 14)
  - Medical Center Alumni Conference, 1956-1967 (Box 14)
  - Michigan Art Fairs and Shows 1978-1980 (Box 14)
  - Michigan Assessors Association
    - IAAO Short Courses, 1977-1980 (Box 14)
    - Eastern Michigan Short Courses for Assessing Personnel, 1974-1977 (Box 14)
    - Middle Michigan Short Course for Assessing Personnel, 1973-1977 (Box 14)
    - Middle Michigan Conference for Tax Assessors, 1966-1971 (Box 14)
    - Short Courses for Assessing Officers, 1947-1989, 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Upper Peninsula Conference for Assessing Officers, 1954-1971 (Box 14)
    - Upper Peninsula Short Courses for Assessing Personnel, 1972-1977 (Box 14)
    - Western Michigan Short Courses for Assessing Personnel, 1972-1977 (Box 14)
  - Michigan Assessors Training Institute, 1938-1939 (Box 14)
  - Michigan Association Concerned with School-Age Parents 1984-1989 (Box 15)
  - Michigan Association for Educational Data Systems, 1972-1973 (Box 15)
  - Michigan Association for Infant Mental Health 1977-1990 (Box 15)
  - Michigan Association for Church Related Colleges, 1959-1962 (Box 15)
  - Michigan Association of Fire Apparatus Supervisors, 1964-1980 (Box 15)
  - Michigan Association of School Librarians
    - Directories 1962-1963 (Box 15)
    - Miscellaneous Undated (Box 15)
    - Programs 1958-1971 (Box 15)
  - Michigan Association of Student Councils
    - Miscellaneous Undated (Box 15)
    - Programs
      - Michigan High School Conference on Citizenship, 1949-1954 (Box 15)
      - Student Council Conference for High Schools--Division II, 1960-1968 (Box 15)
      - Student Council Conference for High Schools--Division IV, 1965-1969 (Box 15)
      - Student Council Conference for Junior High Schools, 1958-1970 (Box 15)
      - Student Council Conference for Senior High--Division I, 1955-1970 (Box 15)
      - Upper Peninsula Annual Student Council Conference for High Schools--Division III, 1957-1970 (Box 15)
  - Michigan Association of Student Councils (cont.)
    - Programs (cont.)
      - Upper Peninsula High School Conference on Citizenship, 1949-1952 (Box 15)
  - Michigan Conference on Community Adult and Continuing Education, 1972-1975 (Box 15)
  - Michigan Dietetic Association 1962-1980 (Box 15)
  - Michigan Fire Chief's Training Conference, 1958-1983 (Box 15)
  - Michigan Fire College, 1942-1966 (Box 15)
  - Michigan High School Music Festival, 1934 (Box 15)
  - Michigan Highway Conference, 1953-1973, 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Michigan Library Association 1952-1964 (Box 15)
  - Michigan Pastor's Conference, 1940-1973, 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Michigan Railroads Association 1954-1958 (Box 15)
  - Michigan Regional Foundry Conference, 1952-1958 (Box 15)
  - Michigan Savings and Loan League
    - Addresses 1954 (Box 15)
    - Programs 1951-1954 (Box 15)
  - Michigan Scholar's Conference, 1964-1980 (Box 15)
  - Michigan School Testing Conference, 1962-1988 (Box 15)
  - Midwestern Conference on School Vocal and Instrumental Music, 1946-1979, 5 folders (Box 16)
  - Modulated Semiconductor Structures, 1989 (Box 16)
  - Motor Fleet Supervisor Training Course
    - Brochures 1948-1957 (Box 16)
    - Programs 1949-1956 (Box 16)
  - Municipal Finance Training Institute, 1954-1974 (Box 16)
  - Municipal Purchasing Conference, 1952-1968 (Box 16)
  - National University Extension Association
    - Annual Meetings 1967 (Box 16)
    - Proceedings 1924-1925, 2 folders (Box 16)
  - Non-Academic Job Hunting for Graduate Students, 1974-1978 (Box 16)
  - Occupational Education Program 1974-1980 (Box 16)
  - Office of the 80s/90s, 1980-1991 (Box 16)
  - Overstreet Program, 1945-1956 (Box 16)
  - Parent Education Institute
    - Addresses 1932-1933 (Box 16)
    - Proceedings 1939 (Box 16)
    - Programs 1932-1958, 2 folders (Box 16)
  - Pharmacy Day, 1960-1965 (Box 16)
  - Program Planning Institute, 1949-1951 (Box 16)
  - Quality Concrete Conference, 1967-1968 (Box 16)
  - Quality Control by Statistical Methods, 1948-1958 (Box 16)
  - Radio Television News Directors Association, 1973-1974 (Box 16)
  - Regional Art Exhibition and Art Conference, 1958-1977 (Box 16)
  - Research Reviews in Chemistry, 1968-1969 (Box 16)
  - School of Business Administration
    - Brochures 1945-1946 (Box 16)
    - Courses
      - Hardware Sales Study Course, 1951-1955 (Box 16)
      - Study Course on Consumer Finance Management Problems, 1953-1955 (Box 16)
  - School of Business Administration (cont.)
    - Programs
      - Alumni Conference, 1952-1953 (Box 16)
      - Merchandising Conference, 1949-1955 (Box 16)
  - School of Dentistry 1970-1973 (Box 16)
  - School of Library Science 1976-1980 (Box 16)
  - School of Music
    - Concert Programs 1942-1966 (Box 16)
    - Programs
      - American Musicological Society, 1958-1965 (Box 16)
      - Annual National Band Conductor's Conference, 1964-1965 (Box 16)
      - Michigan Music Teachers Association, 1964 (Box 16)
      - Michigan Youth Symphony, 1961-1969 (Box 16)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 16)
      - Summer Conference in Music Education, 1971-1972 (Box 16)
      - Summer Workshops in Music Education, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
      - Summer Conference on Piano Teaching, 1960-1965 (Box 16)
  - School of Natural Resources
    - Miscellaneous 1956-1980 (Box 16)
    - Programs
      - Fishing Clinic for Michigan Anglers, 1955-1956 (Box 16)
      - Trouble Shooting in the Wood Working Industry, 1952-1958 (Box 16)
  - School of Nursing
    - Miscellaneous 1949-1961 (Box 17)
    - Programs
      - Clinical Institute for Professional Nurses, 1958-1959 (Box 17)
      - A Conference on Nursing Care of the Critically Ill Patient, 1958-1959 (Box 17)
      - A Conference on Nursing Care of the Premature Infant, 1958-1959 (Box 17)
      - How to Plan for Team Nursing, 1957 (Box 17)
      - Institute on Operating Room Nursing, 1956 (Box 17)
      - Michigan League for Nursing Annual Meeting, 1963-1964 (Box 17)
      - Michigan Nurses Association, 1967-1968 (Box 17)
  - School of Public Health
    - Brochures 1978-1979 (Box 17)
    - Courses
      - Courses in Public Health, 1975-1981 (Box 17)
      - Short Course on Radiation Protection Surveys, 1972-1976 (Box 17)
    - Miscellaneous 1958-1981 (Box 17)
    - Programs
      - Alumni Days, 1971-1977 (Box 17)
  - School of Social Work
    - Bulletins 1953-1981 (Box 17)
    - Continuing Education Program in the Human Services
      - Bulletins 1970-1990, 3 folders (Box 17)
    - Miscellaneous 1943-1983 (Box 17)
  - Seminar and Training Course in Arson Detection and Investigation, 1958-1980 (Box 17)
  - Seminar for Community College Presidents and Trustees, 1975-1977 (Box 17)
  - Seminar on Urban Higher Education, 1975 (Box 17)
  - Senior High Student Leadership Conference, 1976-1979 (Box 17)